

Sandy Lin

4F., No. 180, Wanda Rd., Wanhua Dist., Taipei City, Taiwan +886-903142316 | +886-958284776

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sandy-l-b97150117/ | https://sandylin520.github.io/RS/b810521@gmail.com

SUMMARY

My past experience focuses on B-to-B Service, it equips me with hands-on experience relating to project administration, service management, order management, auditing and billing domain. I provided a high-level technical support to reduce engineering workload, troubleshoot system problems to ensure the accuracy of the cash flow and mail delivery.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Underwriters Laboratories| Client Service Specialist

Taipei, Taiwan | September 2015 - May 2021

Key Responsibilities

- Managed 53 product categories in domestic wire and cable industry.
- Assisted customers with project management and assisted local collection team to ensure accuracy of invoices to meet cash flow targets
- Built up new service knowledge to align with division business strategies
- Participated in trade shows and technical conferences, presented obtained knowledge and information to team or coworkers after the event
- Determined customer needs and guided them to make decisions about product certification
- Provided training to colleagues on programs and processes, technical support to in house employees
- Collaborated and coordinated with Operations, Support Services, Quality Assurance, Sales, Business Development and other affiliated stakeholders to ensure that clients experience superior service.
- Supported global team to implement system successfully
- Classified customers, updated and maintained customer database (Internal oracle database, MyUL Product IQ, My UL Portal)
- Provided quotes, organized and processed samples for assigned client accounts

Key Achievement

- Achieved referral business opportunity target \$15K across division
- Met 90% of assigned myUL email campaign customer registered
- Encouraged 150+ clients to register for new platform, MyUL Portal in 2019
- Met internal KPI target (92% of Engineer Support team e-Mail responses within 24hrs & 94% of personal e-Mail responses within 24hrs in 2015~2021)
- Supported Sales to help key account customers register MyUL successfully (100%)
- Supported global team to implement system successfully, MyUL Portal, Product iQ, ECM

Ezfly International Travel Agent Co Ltd | Wholesaler

Taipei, Taiwan | March 2015 - September 2015

- Sold group tours and tour packages to retail travel agents
- Participated in travel exhibitions and sold tours to customers
- Reached highest monthly sales revenue record: NT\$ 1 million

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration Exchange Student Program

LANGUAGE

Chinese: Native English: Fluent German: Basic

SKILLS

MS Office, Customer Satisfaction, Project management, Teamwork, Communication, Oracle Python, SQL

INTERESTS

Build websites (https://sandylin520.github.io/RS/), and research Python used in business processes

CERTIFICATION

TOEIC 875, IELTS 6.5(2021/1/23)